[
  [
    {
      "question": "Takım çalışmasında rolünüz nedir?",
      "answer": "Lider"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zorluklarla karşılaştığınızda ne yaparsınız?",
      "answer": "Sakin kalırım"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Takım çalışmasında rolünüz nedir?",
      "answer": "Lider"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zorluklarla karşılaştığınızda ne yaparsınız?",
      "answer": "Sakin kalırım"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Takım çalışmasında rolünüz nedir?",
      "answer": "Destekleyici"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zorluklarla karşılaştığınızda ne yaparsınız?",
      "answer": "Hızlı çözüm bulurum"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Takım çalışmasında rolünüz nedir?",
      "answer": "Lider"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zorluklarla karşılaştığınızda ne yaparsınız?",
      "answer": "Sakin kalırım"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Takım çalışmasında rolünüz nedir?",
      "answer": "Bağımsız"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zorluklarla karşılaştığınızda ne yaparsınız?",
      "answer": "Hızlı çözüm bulurum"
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Takım çalışmasında rolünüz nedir?",
      "answer": "Destekleyici"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zorluklarla karşılaştığınızda ne yaparsınız?",
      "answer": "Hızlı çözüm bulurum"
    }
  ]
]
